{
    "subject": "resource/John_Timbs",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:English_antiquarians",
    "human_readable": "John Timbs is an English antiquarian.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9112381935119629,
            "question": "Are there any famous English antiquarians besides John Timbs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5359693169593811,
            "question": "What nationality is John Timbs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.486339807510376,
            "question": "Can you give an example of what an English antiquarian studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40890195965766907,
            "question": "What field of study is John Timbs known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3931277096271515,
            "question": "What resources might John Timbs use in his research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3481968939304352,
            "question": "What are some topics that John Timbs might research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31824204325675964,
            "question": "What skills and qualities would be important for a successful English antiquarian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27804601192474365,
            "question": "How could John Timbs' work contribute to our understanding of history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27222153544425964,
            "question": "How does the work of an antiquarian differ from that of a historian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23710955679416656,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by antiquarians today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Timbs is an English antiquarian.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2511_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the work of an antiquarian differ from that of a historian?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2511_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How could John Timbs' work contribute to our understanding of history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2511_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What skills and qualities would be important for a successful English antiquarian?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2511_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2511_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about John Timbs, and it states that he was an English author and aficionado of antiquities, which implies that he is an antiquarian. Therefore, the triple is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about John Timbs, confirming that he was an English author and antiquary. Therefore, the statement \"John Timbs is an English antiquarian\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}